Aman Khandelwal

MERN Stack Developer | Backend Developer | Android Developer Alwar, Rajasthan, India

aman.khandelwal1205@gmail.com

**** 9261638242

in

linkedin.com/in/aman-khandelwal-1205

GitHub - https://github.com/amankhandelwal02

Portfolio - https://amankhandelwal.me/

Summary

I'm Aman Khandelwal, currently pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering. I am a Full Stack Web Developer and a Digital Marketer, having expertise in HTML, CSS (Bootstrap & Tailwind CSS), JavaScript (jQuery), React Js (Next Js), Node Js, MongoDB. Other than this, I have also done projects in PHP, Laravel, Python, Django and Flask. I'm a MERN Stack Developer as well, deep interest in Mobile App Development with React Native as well. Moreover, I'm a Freelancer and my services included Software Development & Complete Digital Marketing services.

Experience



Freelancer

Flaanzo Technologies

May 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Freelancing services includes Software Development and Digital Marketing. Within a very short span of 1 Year, I have completed more than 7 successful projects, resulting in happy & long-term collaboration with our clients.

- Website Development
- Cross Platform App Development
- · Complete Digital Marketing

For service related query email at flaanzotechnologies@gmail.com

678 Website Frontend Developer

Tractor Junction

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021 (6 months)

The work responsibilities include the website front end development using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript. Along with the front end, I had also handled website backend using Laravel (PHP) and MySQL database.

Education

MITRC College, Alwar

Bachelor of Technology - B.Tech, Computer Science Engineering 2019 – 2023

I'm Aman Khandelwal, pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering. I am a MERN Stack Developer, Android Developer, Digital Marketer, and a Freelancer providing Software Development & Digital Marketing services.

Licenses & Certifications

- **Server-side Development with NodeJS, Express and MongoDB** Microsoft
- Modern Application Development with Node.js on AWS Specialization Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Full-Stack Web Development with React Specialization Coursera
- Introduction to Web Development with HTML, CSS and JavaScript IBM
- Google Digital Unlocked The Fundamental of Digital Marketing Google Digital Garage
- Google Analytics for Beginners Google Analytics

Skills

- Frontend Development Backend Development Android Development Server Administration HTML5
- · Cascading Style Sheet (CSS) · Bootstrap · Tailwind CSS · JavaScript · ¡Query · AJAX · React.js · Next.js
- Node.js Mongo DB API Development Database Management System (DBMS) React Native Python
- Firebase
 Android Studio
 WordPress

Projects

LinkedIn Clone

This LinkedIn Clone is a exact replica of original LinkedIn wen app with a basic functionality of adding a Post, Like and a full fledge authentication system. The technology used behind in this app includes React.js, Tailwind CSS, Styled Components, Material UI and firebase for database and authentication. The application lets the user to add a post to the feed and even have conversations just like original

one.

Project Link - https://linkedin-clone-20004.firebaseapp.com/

Text Utils

Text Utils is a text utility React application that facilitates the user. to manipulate the text such as turning the text into Uppercase, Lowercase, Titlecase and remove extra spaces.

Project Link - https://amankhandelwal02.github.io/textutils/

Medi Compare

Medi Compare is an online pharma that facilitates the users to browse, buy and compare medicine based on the diseases or symptoms they have, among the different platforms available in India. This dynamic website is made with pure HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript and Firebase database.

Project Link - https://amankhandelwal02.github.io/medi-compare/index.html

Notes App

This is a simple note made with complete HTML, CSS and JavaScript. The application lets the user to take some notes by adding a title and description and also deleting the notes.

Project Link - https://amankhandelwal02.github.io/notes-taking-app/